One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time,
and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
I Love My Country
So it hasn't rained for three years.
What of it?
I have faith in His Majesty,
as does most of the country.
So many times...
So many times I tried to stop them.
But they never listened to me.
The rebellion won't stop.
But they've about reached their limit.
They intend to settle things once
and for all with their next attack.
Their backs are to the wall...
They're prepared to die!
Please, Vivi-chan !
You have to stop those fools!
Katorea
– Where's our leader?
– Inside.
Uncle Toto, rest assured...
Vivi-chan...
...we will stop the rebellion.
Thank you!
So long, Vivi-chan.
This is goodbye for now.
When the city is up and running,
come and visit sometime.
I will, Uncle Toto!
We'll build an awesome city that'll
increase this country's greenery!
Bye, Vivi!
Grow up to be a great princess!
Yeah!
Koza!
I've contacted everyone in the other towns.
This is it.
The time to strike has come.
Yes. We don't have nearly
enough weapons, though.
Even so, it's now or never.
The only ones who can
protect this country...
are us!
I won't let you have her!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Some bodyguards, huh?
There are more of 'em?!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Damn! She got away!
The ruins are that way! Catch her!
Don't let 'em go!
Move!
What in the world?!
Hey! What happened to you?!
What happened here?!
Some bad guys... were after Vivi...
What?!
Grown-ups with blades...
They just went into the ruins!
Koza chased after 'em too!
What?!
– Oh, Princess!
– Where are you, Princess?
Where the hell are you hiding?
Find her! Find her!
Don't let her get away!
Princess Vivi! Come on out!
Oh, there you are!
Please, be a good girl
and get kidnapped already.
Not so fast!
Leader!
You alright, Vivi?!
Ow... Ouch!
Don't underestimate
the Sand-Sand Clan, villain!
Leave this city at once!
Look here, boy.
Just shut it and give up the princess.
You should know better
than to piss off grown-ups.
A blade! Let's run away, Leader!
– That doesn't scare me!
– Huh?!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Leader! Don't do this!
You wanna fight, huh?
Leader!
That punk knocked out the boss!
What the hell?!
Let's put the hurt on 'im!
Alright! C'mere!
Hey, you!
You cretins!
Daddy! Igaram!
Your Highness! Are you all right?!
Curse you!
Thought you could
kidnap my daughter, did you?!
You lousy vagabonds!
Take this! And this! And this!
These appear to be their friends.
Chaka! Pell!
What are you doing here?
Why? We could ask you
the same thing.
What is the king doing in a place
like this, away from the palace?
You should refrain
from acting so recklessly.
Igaram! Koza's hurt!
Yes! A doctor should tend to him immediately!
The Sand-Sand Clan members
atop the hill, too!
Chaka! Pell!
Make arrangements at once!
Yes, sir!
What brave children!
What is the matter, Vivi?
Why so glum?
I was so scared...
Yeah, I was scared too.
They even had blades on them...
That's not it!
You told them to protect me
to the death, Leader...
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Don't talk about dying, Leader...
Oh, more than anything,
she was afraid of losing her friends.
Vivi may be young,
but she is also a princess, Koza.
The enormity of your deed today
will not go unnoticed.
You have my gratitude. Thank you.
Vivi's a friend. It was only natural.
Indeed.
I can tell the next generation
of Arabasta will be in good hands.
Do you like this country?
Yeah! It's my homeland!
I feel the same!
Though I...
I am also a bit concerned.
How so?
Your high position ceaselessly asks
that you make difficult decisions.
Vivi-sama is too kindhearted for that.
Igaram.
Yes, sire?
This is fine. Arabasta is
fine just as it is now.
Allow me to accompany you,
for as long as I live!
Yuba?
Yeah! Your dad talked
to my dad about it!
Uncle Toto?
He was asked to break new ground
at the uninhabited Yuba Oasis.
Yuba
That area's like
the crossroads of Arabasta,
where every traveler
and merchant pass through!
Yuba
Yubaba
Just wait till it's built
and becomes a city!
Yubaba
Yubaubaba
Yuba
Yubaubaa
It'll make so many citizens happy!
Yuba
Yuba uba
Yubaa
Yubaubaa
Yuba
Awesome, huh?!
And my dad was asked
to be its representative!
Are you going too, Leader?
Of course!
My dad wants me to stay here...
I'm sure starting a city isn't easy...
but I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna build a new city
with my own two hands!
Yuba's exactly what
this country needs!
Make us proud, Toto.
Yes, Your Majesty!
We will build a wonderful city!
So long, Vivi-chan.
This is goodbye for now.
When the city is up and running,
come and visit sometime.
I will, Uncle Toto!
We'll build an awesome city that'll
increase this country's greenery!
Time to go!
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Yeah!
Koza! You're too casual with her!
Ow!
Koza is right.
Yuba will surely increase
this country's greenery.
Excellent work today, my good men!
So let's hit the hay for now and
regain our strength for tomorrow!
Nighty-night!
You've been sleeping all day!
Why, you...
I don't have the endurance
of you monsters!
Now you've done it!
Besides, you win today's
laziness award, Blue Nose!
I'm not built for hot weather!
Sanji-san. That's my–
Yes. I thought you might have a
hard time sleeping alone tonight.
And just what are you up to, mister?
Oh, that took some nerve.
Which one of you
is spoiling for a fight?!
Do you guys not understand
the point of shut-eye?!
That's it! You're in trouble now!
Hey, old guy. There's still no water.
My throat's bone-dry...
How do you even live here?
This is bad.
There'll be water.
The Yuba Oasis yet lives.
Yuba, you see, can't be beaten
by some lousy sand!
I'll dig it back up
as many times as it takes!
The king himself entrusted me
with this very important land.
Oh, okay! If so, let's dig!
Oh! Wait! Stop!
Don't refill the hole I just dug!
Are you trying to fill the holes?!
No, I'm digging.
No! The sand you're digging up is landing in the hole I just dug,
so I'm trying to say that all my
hard work will be for nothing!
Oh.
Oh! So it's a mystery hole!
Not even close!
Actually, the sand isn't
flying this way now.
All this, in such a short time?!
Despite being tired
from a long journey...
May you rest well tonight.
Meat...
Pleasant dreams.
Casino
Rain Dinners
Nobody's clowning here!
Just how long are you
going to make us wait?!
The least you could do
is offer me an octopar!
Don't make me dance! I'm a swan!
Don't make me spin around!
Mr. 2, please wait quietly.
Seriously! You imbecile! Imba! Imb!
You make my back hurt!
You too, Miss Merry Christmas.
Seems it's too tall an order
to have you get along.
That won't be necessary anyway.
Miss All Sunday...
I want to thank you all for gathering here—
here, where the people
gamble big to win big:
the City of Dreams, Rainbase!
Welcome to Rain Dinners,
the city's largest casino!
Could you skip the formalities and
cut to the chase, Miss All Sunday?
Very well.
I'll get right to the point.
Yeah! Get started! Started!
Start! Sta! Sta! St! St! S!
But before we begin,
allow me to introduce our company's boss, whose face you've never seen.
Up until now, I've worked as his
proxy to dole out assignments,
but there is no longer any need for that.
I take it you understand.
At last, the time has come...
for Operation Utopia.
Crocodile?!
This will be Baroque Works'
ultimate operation.
It would seem you know who he is...
well, outwardly, that is.
Of course we do! But one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
We really got ourselves
a big shot here!
All this time, we've been
kissing up to a pirate?!
You're our boss?
Dissatisfied?
Not exactly dissatisfied,
but the Seven Warlords
are government-sanctioned pirates.
Why even run
this kind of outfit?
What I want is neither money nor status.
I want military might.
Military might?
Allow me to explain in good order...
my true objective...
and the entire breakdown of
Baroque Works' ultimate operation.
Something like that really
exists in this country?
And we'll steal the entire country
along with it?
I've got chills running through me!
To clarify, each task we carried out
was all part of your grand plan?
That's exactly right.
Since Baroque Works was founded,
each job you carried out brought
this operation ever closer to fruition.
And those letters are your final orders.
At long last, the Kingdom
of Arabasta will disappear!
When you have each fulfilled your mission,
the Kingdom of Arabasta will self-implode.
And, left with no other choice,
the Rebel and Royal Armies...
will tragically fall into
Baroque Works' hands.
In a single night,
this land will truly become our utopia.
Operation Utopia is Baroque Works'
last and greatest operation.
Failure is not an option.
We begin at noon tomorrow.
Understood!
I wish you luck.
I must ask that you hold off
on this so-called Operation Utopia.
Mr. 3. How did you get
into this secret underground room?
Mr. 3! Just what rock did you
crawl out from under?!
I'll make good on my orders
and take you out!
Wait, Mr. 2.
"Crawl out from under"? How impolite.
Since the Spiders Cafe,
I never strayed from your side.
I even took a ride on Bunchi's car.
Nice to meet you, Boss.
I've come here to humbly ask
for another chance.
After I failed to accomplish
my given task, Mr. 2,
it was only natural that you'd be
swiftly dispatched to end my life.
So I slightly adjusted course
and headed for the Spiders Cafe,
where we agents are stationed.
Failed to accomplish your task?
What are you talking about?
You know. H-How I let the
Straw Hats and Princess Vivi escape–
"Escape," you say?!
Then you're telling me
they're still alive?!
What was it you said
over the transponder snail?
Did you not tell me you personally took care of the pirates and Vivi?!
Transponder snail?
Wh-What do you mean?
I never used a transponder snail
while on Little Garden.
What?!
Heya, you've reached
Restaurant de Merde.
Making a reservation?
This isn't good.
So that's why the Unluckies
never returned from the island.
But, I'm sure you at least rid us
of a pirate or two?
N-No, actually...
Y-You see, our intelligence report
was incomplete!
She actually had four pirate escorts,
and there... there was
also a long-nosed man, and–
Damn you!
Zero-chan ! Come on,
he's obviously just clowning around.
None of it makes any sense!
I... I met them!
I ran into these guys on my way here!
What?!
Him! Him!
Her!
Him!
And him, right?!
And...
this is Miss Wednesday,
who is this kingdom's Princess Vivi!
Meaning they were actually our enemy?!
Yes. They know my identity.
They will interfere
with the operation if left alone.
And Mr. 3.
It's as you say; there is one
more person, including an animal.
Setting the pet aside,
it's safe to assume Vivi and the other four... are already here in Arabasta.
Mr. 2, photograph those faces
your memory feature recorded.
B-But, Boss!
I swear that I will take care of
that crew and Vivi with my own two–
Quiet, you damn fool!
Mr. 3...
Mr. 3!
Do you know why
I gave you your rank?!
In terms of fighting skill alone,
even Mr. 4 outclasses you, Mr. 3!
It was due to that...
underhanded, contemptible tenacity with which you carry out your tasks!
You've really let me down!
Wh-What is that?!
H-He's drying up!
W-Water...
Water...
Have all the water you want.
Time for dinner.
What is this place? Underwater?
I-It's almost like an aquarium...
A b-bananagator!
That sniveling weakling's
complicated things...
He just doesn't know
how to stay dead!
Listen, now!
Take a good look at these five!
They'll stop at nothing to end the rebellion.
If we leave them alone,
they'll eventually come to us!
But, Zero-chan.
Even if she is the princess,
do you really think she can stop
the rebellion at this point?
Unfortunately, our
intel tells us that...
the rebel leader Koza and Princess
Nefertari Vivi are longtime friends.
It's a swell of 700,000.
Even if it can't be easily stopped,
she can bring confusion
to the Rebel Army.
I've already had many
of our billions infiltrate their ranks.
There's been
no communication from them,
which means they've
still delayed any direct action.
Whatever the cost,
Vivi and the Rebel Army...
cannot make contact
before the operation.
– Miss All Sunday.
– Yes?
Given the circumstances,
we can use the transponder snails.
Contact the billions in Nanohana.
Give the order to kill on sight.
Do not let Princess Vivi
and the pirates into Katorea!
Vivi and Koza must not
be allowed to meet!
Yes. Right away.
You all get a move on too! You don't
want to be late for the party!
Our utopia is within our grasp.
I will not abide further trouble.
Please leave it to us, Boss!
You can count on us!
Go enjoy yourselves!
I'm sorry for being
so unseemly, Vivi-chan.
No, nothing of the sort!
Well, Uncle, we should be off!
Oh, Luffy-kun.
Take this with you.
Wow! Water!
Water!
You found some?!
Last night, just after you
fell asleep while digging,
I reached a moist layer of sand.
That water is the moisture
I managed to extract from it!
Oh! That sounds
pretty complicated, but thanks!
It's genuine Yuba water!
I'm sorry it's all I could get.
I'll drink it with care!
Luffy! What're you doing?!
Luffy?
What's wrong, Luffy-san ?
I quit.
Huh?
You "quit"?
Luffy-san... What do you mean?
C'mon, Luffy!
We know you often act on a whim,
but there's no time for this! Get up!
Aren't we going back?
That's right.
Stopping the revolt means going to Katorea,
which is back the way we came.
A million citizens are gonna clash
and make a mess of this country!
This is for Vivi-chan! Now Let's go!
That's boring.
Say what?!
Vivi!
Yes?
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
If we stop the people rebelling,
will that stop Crocodile?
Besides, it's not like we can
really do much in Katorea.
After all, we're pirates. Things are
better off without us around.
Even if he's a moron,
he makes a good point.
That's Luffy for you.
T-That's–
You want to prevent people
from dying in this battle.
None of the citizens...
and none of us!
Even when facing a warlord of the
sea and a million people going wild,
you hope everyone
will stay safe and sound.
Isn't that being naive?
Hold on, Luffy!
Cut Vivi some slack already!
Wait, Nami-san.
But...
Is it so wrong to want such a thing?
Have I erred,
not wanting people to die?!
People die.
Don't give me that!
Keep speaking and you'll pay!
That's exactly what
we're trying to stop here!
The Rebel Army, the Royal Army,
and regular citizens
have done nothing to deserve this!
So why do people have to die...
when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
– Whoa, Luffy! You're going too far!
– Damn it, Luffy!
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
Tell what?!
...what most needs... to be done!
Yuba, you see, can't be
beaten by some lousy sand!
Do you think it's enough
to risk your life alone?
Then what should I be risking?!
I can't let him get away with this!
I've got–
I've got nothing else to give...
Why don't you try risking
all of our lives together!
Aren't we crewmates?!
Aren't we crewmates?
So, you're able to cry
those kinds of tears after all.
We will stop the rebellion!
I know you actually hate this
and want to beat him up the most!
Now tell me...
where Crocodile is!
Video Editing, Gigglebot
Timing, DraSleek, PhosCity
Quality Control, Galaxy 9000, JT-421, Pepperjack
Soundtracking, Halee
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing, Zenef
Translation, DemonRin, FUNimation